ASHIS KUMAR DEY

UI DEVELOPER



- **8**249770133
- ✓ ashisdey128@gmail.com
- 2 16/95g, Raghunathpur, Baripada Mayurbhanj, Odisha

PROFILE

Passionate UI developer having 3+ years experience in web development using HTML, CSS, SCSS, javascript, and angular js. I also worked with various css library like bootstrap. I worked for clients like fly dubai, and Kimberly Clark.

SKILLS

- UI development
- HTML, CSS
- Angular js
- Angular 8
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- GIT Tools
- Strong Communication

EXPERIENCE

UI DEVELOPER

Cognizant technology solutions

2021 - Present

- Worked as programmer analyst by creating various websites and software for global clients. Worked on 4 projects with technology like html, CSS javascript, bootstrap and jQuery.
- Also worked for website performance optimization.

UI DEVELOPER

Tapplent technology solutions

2021

- Worked for a product which having varios dashboard using angular 8, Material design for varios data display and content visualisation.
- Created various websites for clients

UI DEVELOPER

Flynavara technology solutions

2019 - 2021

- Worked for inhouse product to determine pricing solution for airlines
- Created various dashboard and chats with angular js and bootstrap with HTML & CSS

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Jupiter +2 science college, Bhubaneswar 2013- 2015

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

Biju Patnaik University of technology, odisha 2015 - 2019